topbun.com 2017-03-29

# Myspace Layouts - Myspace Graphics - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Please read our privacy policy when you use our codes or content in other websites like myspace, hi5, xanga or any other website.

Use of the topbun.com website indicates your agreement to our terms set forth in this privacy policy.

**Information Automatically Logged**

Once you’ve entered any page on the site your IP address is automatically logged in our log files, along with your ISP, the type of browser you use to browse topbun.com, and which pages were visited. This information is used to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site such as providing new and up-to-date content that is in demand by our users.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
topbun.com the website does not use cookies to store information. However, we do use Third-Party advertising companies to help support our site. These advertisers may use cookies and web beacons when displaying advertisements on topbun.com for the use of displaying ads. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by the third-party ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some of the information collected from cookies may include the users IP address, ISP, Browser and Location. Location is generally used for geo-targeting; Which allows the advertisers to show the user advertisements from their region or geographical location.

Additionaly you may opt to turn cookies off by adjusting the privacy settings either in your browser, Firewall or Anti-Virus software.

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**Third Party Advertisers**

We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of third party advertising links within our site.

Third party advertisers may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. 

**Limitations on privacy**

We reserve the right to provide information if there is a violation of our terms of service. 

We respect the privacy of our users and protect it with our best efforts, but please understand that there are risks in using the Internet. There is always the possibility of personal information being accessed by intruders and privacy cannot be fully guaranteed.
